Franklin-Bache Papers 1707-1799 Mss.B.F85.ba
American Philosophical Society
- Franklin-Bache Papers, 1707-1799; B F85.ba; 4 lin. feet
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 April 25; Hewson, Mary Stevenson
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 April 29; Barclay, Thomas
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 April 29; Hillegas, Michael
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 May 4; Freeborn, Alice
  - Exchange of British-American Prisoners, 1782 May 8
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 May 8; Greene, Catherine Ray
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 May 14; Dumas, Charles-Guillaume-Frédéric
  - to Silas Deane, 1782 May 15; Trumbull, Jonathan
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 May 20; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 May 20; Livingston, Robert R., 1746-1813
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 May 23; Hewson, Mary Stevenson
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 May 23; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 May 29; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 May 29; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 May 30; Dumas, Charles-Guillaume-Frédéric
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 June 9; Shipley, Georgiana, d.1806
  - to Jonathan Williams, Jr, 1782 June 13; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 June 13; Putman, B.
  - to Louis XVI, 1782 June 13; U.S. Congress (Oversize X)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 June 15; Cooper, S.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 June 17; Barclay, Thomas
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 June 17; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 June 18; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - to U.S, 1782 June 19; John Lang's Sons
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 June 22; Dumas, Charles-Guillaume-Frédéric
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 June 25; Greene, W. and Catharine
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 June 25; Mecom, Jane (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 June 27; Barclay, Thomas
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 June 28; Dumas, Charles-Guillaume-Frédéric
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 July 1; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 July 5; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 July 8; Carmichael, William, d. 1795
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 July 8; Dumas, Charles-Guillaume-Frédéric
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 July 16; Mildred, D.
  - Benjamin Franklin's account with Ferdinand Grand, 1782 July 17-1783 Jan. 20
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 July 17; Barclay, Thomas
  - Certification by Thomas Price, 1782 July 22
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 July 22; Cooper, S.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 July 23; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 July 23; Hutton, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 July 23; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - to R. and S. Bache, 1782 July 27; Franklin, Benjamin
  - Claim.. .by LeBel and Arena, 1782 July 30
  - to John Hanson, 1782 July 30; Morris, Robert (Oversize 1)
  - Memo of accounts, 1782 July
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 August 1; Vaughan, William
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 August 5; Jones, W.
  - Resultat Gendal de Remises, 1782 August 5
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 August 7; Williamson, H.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 August 9; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 August 10; Burke, Edmund
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 August 12; Barclay, Thomas
  - to F. Grand, 1782 August 12; Wyld, E.
  - to Ferdinand Grand, 1782 August 12; Wyld, E.
  - to [F. Grand], 1782 August 18; Swindell, J.
  - to Ferdinand Grand, 1782 August 20; Wyld, E.
    [See folder for 1782 August 12]
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 August 20; Carmichael, William, d. 1795
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 August 23; Stewart, M.
  - to George Washington, 1782 August 29; Morris, Robert
  - to George Washington, 1782 August 30; Morris, Robert
  - Resolution, 1782 Sept. 3; United States. Congress
  - to George Washington, 1782 Sept. 9; Morris, Robert
  - Resolution, 1782 Sept. 9; United States. Congress
  - Resolution, 1782 Sept. 10; United States. Congress
  - to Robert Morris, 1782 Sept. 11; Contractors for supplies for Army (Oversize 1)
  - Congressional Resolutions, 1782 Sept. 14, 23 (Oversize 1)
  - Congressional Resolutions, 1782 Sept. 14, 23 (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Sept. 16; Beall, Samuel
  - Resolution, 1782 Sept. 17; United States. Congress
  - Resolution, 1782 Sept. 17; United States. Congress
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Sept. 20; Juhonnot, S. C.
  - to Ezekiel Cornell, 1782 Sept. 20; Morris, Robert
  - Letter to ----, 1782 Sept. 20
  - to Benjamin Franklin, [1782?] Sept. 20; Shipley, Joseph, 1714-1788
  - Instructions to Robert Barclay, 1782 Sept. 23 (Oversize 1)
  - to Ezekiel Cornell, 1782 Sept. 23; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Sept. 25; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Sept. 25; Morris, Robert
  - to John Adams, 1782 Sept. 27; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Sept. 27; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Sept. 27; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Sept. 28; Morris, Robert
  - to Ezekiel Cornell, 1782 Sept. 29; Swift, Herman
  - to contractors for supplying the army, 1782 Sept. 30; Cornell, Ezekiel
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Sept. 30; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Oct. 1; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Oct. 1; Bache, Sarah
  - to Ezekiel Cornell, 1782 Oct. 1; Comfort Sands and Co. and Walter Livingston contractors for supplying the army
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Oct. 1; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Oct. 2; Shipley, Georgiana, d.1806
  - Resolution, 1782 Oct. 3; United States. Congress
  - Resolution, 1782 Oct. 4; United States. Congress
  - to Robert Morris, 1782 Oct. 5; Cornell, Ezekiel
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Oct. 5; Morris, Robert
  - to Robert Morris, 1782 Oct. 5; Tilghman, Tench
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Oct. 7; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Oct. 7; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Oct. 7; Morris, Robert
  - to contractors for supplying the army, 1782 Oct. 10; Morris, Robert
  - to Ezekiel Cornell, 1782 Oct. 10; Morris, Robert
  - Contract for army supplies, 1782 Oct. 12; Robert Morris, Jeremiah Wadsworth, and John Carter. (Oversize 1)
  - Resolution, 1782 Oct. 17; United States. Congress
    [see folder for 1782 Oct. 4]
  - Resolution, 1782 Oct. 17; United States. Congress
  - to the Governors of the several states, 1782 Oct. 21; Morris, Robert (Oversize 1)
  - to John Hanson, 1782 Oct. 21; Morris, Robert (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Oct. 26; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Oct. 27; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Oct. 29; Pearce, J.
  - Notification of C.C. of election of Elias Boudinot as president, 1782 Nov. 4
  - Resolution, 1782 Nov. 12; United States. Congress
  - Resolution, 1782 Nov. 12; United States. Congress
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Nov. 15; Jones, W.
  - General view of public monies, 1782 Nov. 18 (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Nov. 18; Price, Richard, 1723-1791
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Nov. 27; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Nov. 27; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Nov. 27; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Dec. 3; Bache, Sarah
  - Resolution, 1782 Dec. 3; United States. Congress
  - Resolution, 1782 Dec. 6; United States. Congress
  - to G. Johonnot, 1782 Dec. 20; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Dec. 30; Bache, Richard
  - Resolution, 1782 Dec. 31; United States. Congress
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1782 Dec. 31; Vaughan, Benjamin
  - [1782?], Laporte, Jacques
  - [1782], Raspe, R. E.
  - Resolution, 1783 Jan. 1; United States. Congress
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Jan. 2; Bache, Sarah
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Jan. 3; Jefferson, Thomas.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Jan. 3; Sargent, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Jan. 3; Morris, Robert
  - to William Temple Franklin, 1783 Jan. 9; Laurens, H.
  - Resolution, 1783 Jan. 10; United States. Congress
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Jan. 11; Morris, Robert (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Jan. 13; Hewson, Mary Stevenson
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Jan. 13; Morris, Robert
  - to Chev. de la Luzerne, 1783 Jan. 13; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Jan. 14; Lee, S.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Jan. 19; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Jan. 24; Bache, Sarah
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Jan. 24; Hutton, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Jan. 26; Bondfield, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Jan. 28; Sargent, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Jan. 28; Duche, J.
  - Blank passport for a British vessel, 1783 Feb. 1
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Feb. 3; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Feb. 4; Hartley, D.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Feb. 7; Beckhouse, T.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Feb. 7; Wright, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Feb. 18; Baldwin, C.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Feb. 25; Penn, R.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 March 5; Shipley, Joseph, 1714-1788
  - to Vergennes, 1783 March 9; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 March 11; Vaughan, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 March 12; Brocklesby, R.
  - to M. Tarle, 1783 March 12; Morris, Robert (Oversize 1)
  - to Chev. de la Luzerne, 1783 March 14; Morris, Robert
  - to Robert Morris, 1783 March 14; de la Luzerne, Chev.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 March 16; Bache, W.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 March 16; Delamarche, J. W.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 March 18; McIntosh, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 March 25; Geib, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 March 25; Hodgson, William
  - Resolution, 1783 April 1; United States. Congress
  - Resolution, 1783 April 15; United States. Congress
  - Resolution, 1783 April 15; United States. Congress (Oversize 1)
  - Resolution, 1783 April 18; United States. Congress
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 April 18; Hodgson, W.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 April 24; Shipley, Joseph, 1714-1788
  - Resolution, 1783 April 28; United States. Congress
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 April 29; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 April 30; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 April 30; Bache, Richard (Oversize 1)
  - Resolution, 1783 May 2; United States. Congress
  - Resolution, 1783 May 2; United States. Congress
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 May 2; Hutton, J.
  - to Elias Boudinot, 1783 May 3; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 May 6; Whatley, G.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 May 8; Bache, Sarah
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 May 8; Benezet, Anthony, 1713-1784
  - 1783 May 9, Potts, Samuel
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 May 12; Morris, Robert (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 May 19; Price, Richard, 1723-1791
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 May 26; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 May 27; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 May 30; Morris, Robert
  - 1783 May 31, Bache and Shee
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 June 1; Bache, Sarah
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 June 1; Sargent, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 June 11; Owen, O.
  - Resolution, 1783 June 12; United States. Congress (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 June 12; Price, Richard, 1723-1791
  - to B. Harrison, 1783 June 12; Newsclippings; Washington, George (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 June 16; Vaughan, Benjamin
  - Resolution, 1783 June 21; United States. Congress
  - Mutineers of 3rd Penna. Regiment to Supreme Executive Council of Penna, [1783 June 21]
  - to James Chrystie, 1783 June 23; Bennet, James
  - Elias Boudinot Proclamation by, 1783 June 24
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 June 24; Hodgson, W.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 June 24; Vaughan, Benjamin
  - 1783 June 25, Todd, Anthony
  - to S. Moylan, 1783 June 26; Sullivan, J.
  - to S. Moylan, 1783 June 30; Sullivan, J.
  - By the Continental Congress. Extract from minutes, 1783 July 1 (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 July 14; Churchill, C.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 July 15; Lettsom, J. C.
  - to A. Hudson de Levan, 1783 August 10; Franklin, Benjamin
  - 1783 August 15, Potts. S.
  - 1783 August 22, Todd, Anthony
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 August 30; Lafayette, Marie Joseph Paul Yves, marquis de, 1757-1834
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Sept. 7; West, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Sept. 8; Jackson, Charles
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Sept. 9; Bache, Sarah
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Sept. 13; Button, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Sept. 17; Carrel
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Sept. 17; Morris, Robert
  - 1783 Sept. 19, Todd, Anthony
  - to -----, 1783 Sept. 27; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to F. Coffyn, 1783 Oct. 4; Barclay, Thomas
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Oct. 6; Pownall, Thomas
  - To A. Todd, 1783 Oct. 9
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Oct. 11; Coffyn, F.
  - 1783 Oct. 17, Todd, Anthony
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Oct. 20; Childs, Francis, 1763-1830
  - To A. Todd, 1783 Oct. 29
  - Address by P. J. Van Berkel, 1783 Oct. 31
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Nov. 4; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Nov. 9; Bache, Richard
  - 1783 Nov. 18, Todd, Anthony
  - Enclosure with letter from A. Todd, 1783 Nov. 18 (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Dec. 20; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Dec. 24; Perkins, W. L.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1783 Dec. 29; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - Explication de la medaille frappee par les Americains en 1782, [1783?]
  - [Memo by Franklin.], [1783-1784]; Arret... (Oversize 1)
  - to John Adams, Benjamin Franklin, John Jay and Henry Laurens, 1784 Jan. 5; Mifflin, Thomas?
  - Resolution, 1784 Jan. 14; United States. Congress
  - Resolution, 1784 Jan. 14; United States. Congress
  - Resolution, 1784 Jan. 14; United States. Congress
  - Congressional Proclamation, 1784 Jan. 14
  - Congressional Proclamation, 1784 Jan. 14
  - to Franklin, Adams and Jay, 1784 Jan. 14; Mifflin, Thomas
  - to Josiah Harmar, [1784 Jan. 14]; Mifflin, Thomas
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Jan. 15; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Jan. 17; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Feb. 1; ----, ----
  - By Robert Morris-Advertisement, 1784 Feb. 9
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Feb. 12; Morris, Robert
  - to Messrs. Wilhelm and Jan Willink, Nicolaas and Jacob Van Staphorst, De la Lande and Finji, 1784 Feb. 12; Morris, Robert
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Feb. 13; Morris, Robert
  - to W. Hodgson, 1784 March 1; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 March 2; Clark, Anne
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 March 10; Martin, B.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 March 17; Imberty
  - to David Hartley, 1784 March 31; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 April 3; Kuppler, S.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 April 3; Kuppler, S.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 April 7; Tournachon
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 April 9; Todd, Anthony
  - 1784 April 9, Todd, Anthony
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 April 28; Bache, Richard
  - to Pere Pagin, 1784 May 4; Milliet, G.
  - to La Luzerne, 1784 May 4; Webster, P.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 May 5; Nairne, E.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 May 7; Barclay, Thomas
  - to Baron d' Ogny, 1784 May 11; Todd, Anthony
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 May 13; Hartley, D.
  - 1784 May 18, Todd, Anthony
  - Copies of papers re Longchamps-Marbois affair, 1784 May 19-June 26
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 May 22; Collinson, T.
  - 1784 May 25 [or 29], d' Ogny, Baron
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 June 8; Grattan, E.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 June 8; Morals of Horace. Enclosed with E. Grattan
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 June 8; Oswald, R.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 June 10; Livingston, W.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 June 12; Childs, Francis, 1763-1830
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 June 21; Hollis, T. B.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, [1784 June]; Bache, Sarah
  - to Benjamin Franklin, [1784 June]; Bache, Sarah
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 July 4; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 July 19; Huntington, A.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 August 13; Thomson, Charles
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 August 16; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Sept. 10; Bache, Richard
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Sept. 15; Hutton, J.
  - to -illoust, 1784 Oct. 18; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to -illoust, [1784 Oct. 18]; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Oct. 21; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Oct. 25; Hewson, Mary Stevenson
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Nov. 6; Shipley, Georgiana, d.1806
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Nov. 13; Childs, Francis, 1763-1830
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Nov. 14; Sargent, J.
  - Advertisement, 1784 Nov. 18
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Nov. 18; Viny, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Nov. 19; Banks, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Nov. 19; Nairne, E.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Nov. 20; West, B.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Nov. 21; Strahan, William
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Nov. 21; Vaughan, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Dec. 1; Huntington, A.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Dec. 4; Vergennes
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Dec. 11; Lee, Richard Henry
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Dec. 16; Williams, Jonathan Jr.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Dec. 24; Huntington, S.
  - Statement of purchase of government bonds for Benjamin Franklin, 1784 Dec. 31; Grand, Ferdinand
  - Franklin's Daylight Saving Plan, [1784?]
  - [1784], Shipley, Joseph, 1714-1788
  - [1784], Shipley, Joseph, 1714-1788
  - to Charles Thomson, [1784 or 1785]; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to [Ferdinand] Grand, 1785 Jan. 9; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to William Temple Franklin, 1785 Jan. 24; Harvey, C.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1785 Jan. 28; Jefferson, Thomas.
  - to R. H. Lee, 1785 Feb. 8; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1785 Feb. 17; Childs, Francis, 1763-1830
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1785 Feb. 23; Vaughan, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1785 March 15; Vaughan, Benjamin
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1785 March 21; Price, Richard, 1723-1791
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1785 March 22; Childs, Francis, 1763-1830
  - Account of U.S. Congress with Benjamin Franklin, 1785 May 4 (Oversize 1)
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1785 May 31; Hutton, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, [1785 May]; Sharp, Granville
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1785 June 30; Chevalier
  - to Chevalier, [1785 June-July]; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Schweighauser and Dobree, 1785 July 10; Franklin, Benjamin
  - Paris stock exchange quotation sheet, 1785 [Sept.?] 18
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1785 Sept. 23; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1785 Oct. 1; Mecom, Jane
  - to [William Temple Franklin], 1785 Oct. 7; Bache, Benjamin Franklin
  - to [William Temple Franklin], Le Ray de Chaumont, J.
  - to [William Temple Franklin], Bache, Sarah
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1785 Oct. 18; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1785 Nov. 7; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1785 Nov. 30; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1785 Dec. 29; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1786 Jan. 6; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1786 Feb. 21,26; Mecom, Jane
  - Shipping Receipt, 1786 March 25
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1786 April 22; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1786 May 3; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1786 May 29; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, [1786 May-June]; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1786 July 21; Mecom, Jane
  - Franklin's memo of accounts, 1786 July [?]
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1786 August 25; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1786 Sept. 13; Mecom, Jane
  - to William Temple Franklin, 1786 Sept. 18; Wilkes, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1786 Oct. 12; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, [1786 Oct.-Nov.]; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1786 Nov. 5; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1786 Dec. 17; Mecom, Jane
  - Memorandum: Directions for Keeping accounts, [1786-1787?]
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1787 Jan. 6; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1787 March 9; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1787 May 22; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1787 August 16; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1787 Nov. 9; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1787 Nov. 11; Collas, J.
  - Memo of bills [?] signed by William Temple Franklin and Benjamin Franklin, [ca. 1787]
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1788 Jan. 8; Mecom, Jane
  - to W. T. Franklin, 1788 March 30; Le Ray de Chaumont, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1788 June 25; Percival, T.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1788 June 25, July 1; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1788 July 16; Collas, J.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1788 August 9; Bache, E.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1788 Sept. 5; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1788 Sept. 26; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1788 Nov. 11; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1788 Nov. 21; Mecom, Jane
  - Franklin's memo of bills signed by order of Maurice and Homassel, 1788 Nov.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1789 April 2; Mecom, Jane
  - Certification of true extracts of documents above, 1789 May 30; Matthews, John
  - to Benjamin Franklin, [1789 June]; Bache, E.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1789 July 23; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1789 August 29; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1789 Sept. 10; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1789 Nov. 24; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1789 Nov. 25; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1789 Dec. 20; LaLuzerne
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1790 Jan. 17; Mecom, Jane
  - to Benjamin Franklin, 1790 Feb. 6; Mecom, Jane
  - Certified copy of Franklin's will and codicil, 1790 May 19; Franklin, Benjamin (Oversize 1)
  - Address by the Municipality of Paris in memory of Benjamin Franklin, [1790?]
  - to James Rees, 1793 May 2; Deed for tract of land.; Howell, Joseph
  - to Garrett Cottringer, 1793 May 2; Deed for tract of land.; Davidson, William
  - to Robert Morris, Jr, 1794 Dec. 6; Deed for tract of land.; Cottringer, Garrett
  - to Robert Morris, Jr, 1794 Dec. 6; Deed for tract of land.; Rees, James
  - to Robert Morris, Jr, 1795 Jan. 7; Land patent. Four folders, 1 patent in each; Commonwealth of Pa. (Oversize X)
  - to Benjamin Franklin Bache, 1798 March 26; Monroe, James, 1758-1831
  - to Robert Morris, Jr, 1798 July 27; Franklin, William Temple
  - to Robert Morris, Jr, 1798 July 31; Franklin, William Temple
  - to W. T. Franklin, 1799 Jan. 1; Deed; Morris, Robert Jr. and wife, Anna (Oversize X)
  - to [W. T.] Franklin, n.d. (Wednesday Morning); Alexander, W. [Jr.]
  - n.d. (Friday), Allen, Mrs.
  - Memo, n.d; Bache, Benjamin Franklin
  - to Abbe de la Roche, n.d. (Sunday morning); Bianchi, Isidoro
    Scope and Contents note
    Includes profile of Franklin (after Nini medallion) drawn with electricity.
  - to Benjamin Franklin, n.d; Boulainvilliers, Marie Madeleine Adrienne, d'Hallencourt Bernard, marquise de
  - Dessein... d' une grande loupe, Charpentier, F. P. (Oversize X)
  - n.d. (Jan. 1), Chalut de Vérin, Elisabeth Varanchan
  - to Benjamin Franklin, n.d; Chalut and Arnous, Abbés
  - to Benjamin Franklin, n.d. (Friday); Chaulnes, Yves Marie Joseph d'Albert d'Aily, duc de
  - Memo. #1, n.d; Chaumont, Jacques-Donatien Leray de, 1725-1803
  - Memo. #2, n.d; Chaumont, Jacques-Donatien Leray de, 1725-1803
  - n.d. (Thursday morning), Doughty, Miss
  - Description de la regle parallele roulants, Eckhardt, A. G. (Oversize 1)
  - n.d. (Saturday), d'Estaing, Charles Henri, comte, 1729-1794
  - to [W. T.] Franklin, n.d. (Saturday, 18th); Feutry, Aimé Ambroise Joseph
  - Fragment, n.d; Franklin, Benjamin
  - Boat for pleasure or fishing parties on the Delaware River, n.d; Watercolor sketch; Franklin, Benjamin (Oversize X)
  - Memo, n.d; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to "Amiable family at Passy.", n.d; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Mrs. Bache, n.d; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to Francesco Favi, n.d; Franklin, Benjamin
  - to William Temple Franklin [memo.], n.d; Franklin, Benjamin
  - Memorandum of account with M. le Ray de Chaumont, Franklin, Benjamin
  - Memo. of account with Mr. Grand, Franklin, Benjamin
  - Memo. of accounts. #1, n.d; Franklin, Benjamin